Now for question one, we had to come up with a plan.
对于第一个问题 我们需要制定一个计划
So I feel like adding audio is going to be similar to adding images to the app
我觉得向应用中添加音频和添加图片应该比较相似
because we have additional pieces of information for each word in the app.
因为应用中的每个单词都需要添加额外的信息
So I read the steps that we did in lesson 3 and
我看了下第 3 节课中的步骤
came up with this summarized list of tasks for adding images the app.
并总结出向应用中添加图片的任务列表
And now I can modify those tasks.
现在我可以修改下这些任务
So that instead of referencing images the tasks apply to adding
任务不再是引用图片 而是向应用中
audio to the app.
添加音频
So our steps are, one, modify list item layout to include a play button.
所以我们的步骤是 第一步 修改列表项布局以便包含播放按钮
Second, handle clicking on a list item to play an audio file.
第二步 点击列表项后播放音频文件
And then we can add in all the audio files.
然后添加所有的音频文件
After that, modify the Word class to store an audio resource ID.
接着 修改 Word 类并存储音频资源 ID
We can play the correct audio file per word.
我们可以为每个单词播放正确的音频文件
And lastly, we can do the fun part of visual polish.
最后是个有趣的环节 即完善应用外观
So let's go ahead and write that in for the answer to question one.
我们将这些步骤写在第一个问题的答案中
All right, so we have a good plan for what steps we need to do.
我们已经制定好需要操作的步骤
Of course, there will always be some more steps that come up as we start
当然 当我们开始编写代码的时候 始终会有更多的步骤
writing the code and realize there's a lot more things we need to take care of.
会发现有更多的任务需要处理
So this list may eventually evolve.
所以这个列表最终可能会有所变化
Now let's move on to the next question how do you play an audio
现在看看第二个问题 如何在 Android 中
file in Android?
播放音频文件呢？
To find an answer you could either ask a fellow Android developer or
要找到答案 你可以问问某位 Android 开发者
just search online for something like play audio Android.
或者直接在网上搜索下 例如“play audio Android”
Now our first result here looks good
第一条搜索结果看起来很有用
because it's from a developer.android.com website.
因为它来自 developer.android.com 网站
Let's click into that.
点开来看看
Now when I come across an article or
当我打开某个文章
tutorial, I don't read through all the details.
或教程时 我不会阅读所有的内容
I know this page can look intimidating because it contains a lot of words that
我知道这个页面看起来比较吓人 里面有好多的术语
you may not recognize.
你可能都不认识
But don't worry,
不用担心
we're just trying to get a high level idea of what we need to use in Android.
我们只是需要大概地知道要在 Android 中使用哪个功能
So you can start off by reading this first paragraph.
可以先阅读第一段内容
Which says that you can play either audio or
上面说到 你可以使用 MediaPlayer 类s
video files using the MediaPlayer class.
来播放音频或视频文件
If you scroll down a bit farther we see this basic section
再往下滚动 我们看到这个基本知识部分
which talks about two classes in Android that you need to use.
这里介绍了 Android 中两个需要使用的类
So it looks like we need something called the MediaPlayer
看起来我们需要使用 MediaPlayer
which is the primary way to play sound in Android.
它是在 Android 中播放音频的主要方式
There's something called an Audio Manager.
还有一个叫做 AudioManager
And I am not sure what that does right now, but we can figure that out later.
现在我还不确定它的作用 但是我们可以稍后去了解下
Now, scrolling down a bit lower it talks about the manifest declarations.
再往下滚动 这里介绍了“Manifest Declarations”
So that's kind of a confusing and unfamiliar phrase for now, so
暂时听起来有点让人困惑 不熟悉
let's skip over that part.
我们跳过这部分
So below that we have the section called Using MediaPlayer and
在下面 有个部分叫做“Using MediaPlayer”
it contains some code snippet examples.
里面包含一些代码段示例
So all this looks pretty useful.
看起来很有用
So we might come back to that later.
我们可能稍后还要回到这部分
Now scrolling through the rest the page there's a bunch of other sections
再往下滚动查看页面的剩余部分 下面还有好多其他几个部分
that looked pretty detailed.
看起来内容非常详细
Some things are easy to recognize and
某些容易看懂
others are a little bit more challenging and that's expected.
其他的则更具挑战性 这很正常
For now we won't read through the rest of the page
暂时我们将不仔细阅读剩下的内容了
there's a lot of good information here that we can come back to
里面有很多有用的信息 当我们编写具体的代码时
when we need the working details of the code.
可以回来参考这些信息
So we did a little bit of research and found that in Android,
我们进行了一些研究 发现在 Android 中
we can use the MediaPlayer class to help us play an audio file.
我们可以使用 MediaPlayer 类来帮助我们播放音频文件
So we don't need to know everything about how it works or
我们不需要知道关于它的所有内容
even how to use it, but at the very least we now know that it exists.
甚至不需要知道如何使用它 但至少知道存在这个类
So we're off to a great start with this feature.
所以对于这项功能 我们有个很好的开端了
But let's keep going.
但还要继续下去